Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XIV is arranged in 7 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XIV. INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS
  - Sub-Series 217-0. International Affairs
    - General, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 27)
      Jan. 1, 1962-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - General, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 28)
      Jan. 1, 1960-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 217-1. International Affairs
    - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1955-1960 (Box 62, Folder 29)
      1955-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 217-2. International Affairs
    - International Labour Conference, Forty-Eighth Session -Report VIII(1):"Employment Policy, with Particular Reference to the Employment Problems of Developing Countries" (bound volume), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - International Labour Conference, Forty-Eighth Session -Report VIII(2):"Employment Policy, with Particular Reference to the Employment Problems of Developing Countries" (bound volume), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - International Labour Conference, Forty-Eighth Session -Report VIII(2):"Employment Policy, with Particular Reference to the Employment Problems of Developing Countries" (bound volume), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - International Labour Conference, Forty-Eighth Session -Report X:"Proposed Declaration concerning the Policy of `Apartheid' of the Republic of South Africa" (bound volume), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - International Labour Conference, Forty-Eighth Session -Report XI:"Inclusion in the Constitution of the International Labour Organization of a Provision Empowering the Conference to Expel or Suspend from Membership Any Member Which Has Been Expelled or Sus, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - International Labour Conference (ILC), Forty-Eighth Session -Report XII:"Inclusion in the Constitution of the International Labour Organization of a Provision Empowering the Conference to Suspend from Participation in the ILC Any Member Which Has Been Fou, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - International Labour Organization. Memorandum on the 48th Session of the International Labour Conference (bound volume), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - International Labour Organization. Supplement to the Memorandum on the 48th Session of the International Labour Conference (bound volume), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - International Labour Office. Minutes of the 160th Session of The Governing Body (bound volume), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 38)
      Nov. 17-20, 1964.
    - International Labor Organization, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 39)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - International Labor Organization, 1958-1962 (Box 62, Folder 40)
      Aug. 15, 1958-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 217-3. International Affairs
    - Refugees, United State Committee for, 1959-1961 (Box 62, Folder 41)
      July 1959-May 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 217-4. International Affairs
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations (A.A.U.N.). George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      Feb. 1, 1963-Aug. 31, 1963.
    - Material on United Nations, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations (A.A.U.N.))-George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      July 16, 1962-Jan. 31, 1963.
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations (A.A.U.N.))-George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      Dec. 15, 1961-July 15, 1962.
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations (A.A.U.N.))-George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      June 1, 1961-Dec. 14, 1961.
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations (A.A.U.N.))-George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      Jan. 1, 1961-May 31, 1961.
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations). George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      May 1, 1960-Dec. 31, 1960.
    - Summary-"Tenth Annual Conference of National Organizations Called by American Association for the United Nations", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      March 6-8, 1960.
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations). George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      Nov. 7, 1959-April 30, 1960.
    - United Nations (American Association for the United Nations). George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Member, Board of Directors, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      1959-Nov. 6, 1959.
    - 217-4(a). United Nations, 1959-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      Jan. 1959-June 1960.
    - 217-4(a). United Nations, 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      July 1958-Jan. 1959.
    - United Nations-George M. Harrison (G.M.H.) Official Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      1958-June 1959.
    - United Nations-Appointment as member U.S. Delegation 13th Session, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      July 1958-Oct. 1958.
    - United Nations-Thirteenth Session of the General Assembly-U.S. Representative George M. Harrison-Speech Material, 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      1958-Feb 1959.
    - 217-4 Section 2. United Nations-Speech Material, 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      1958-Nov. 1959.
    - 217-4 Section 1. United Nations-Speech Material, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - United Nations-Fourteenth Session of the General Assembly-Booklets, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      Oct. 1959.
    - United Nations-Thirteenth Session of the General Assembly-Booklets, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 217-5. International Affairs
    - International Transport Workers Federation (I.T.W.F.)-28th World Congress of the I.T.W.F.-Copenhagen, Denmark, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      July 25-Aug. 6, 1965.
    - International Transport Workers Federation, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1963.
    - International Transport Workers Federation (I.T.W.F.)-27th Congress of the I.T.W.F.- Helsinki, Finland, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      July 25-Aug. 4, 1962.
    - International Transport Workers Federation, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - International Transport Workers Federation, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - International Transport Workers Federation, 1958-1959 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      Aug. 1958-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - International Transport Workers Federation (I.T.W.F.)-Proceedings of the I.T.F.W. Congress (Berne, Switzerland) and the joint report of H.D. Ulrich and F.H. Hall, delegates to the 26th Congress, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 217-6. International Affairs
    - Export-Import Bank of Washington, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Series XV. FOREIGN ORGANIZATIONS
  - Sub-Series 218-14. Foreign Organizations
    - Israel, National Committee for American Trade Union Council (Histradrut), 1962-1964 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      Jan. 1, 1962-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Israel, National Committee for American Trade Union Council, 1955-1961 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      1955-Dec. 31, 1961.